(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
Look at Mom and Dad.
They're still so sweet with each other.
That's what you should dream about.
Like Mom.
All that love stuff!
The only thing on my mind
is for you to finish your studies.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing here?
Did you follow me?
I'll return your money.
-Mikoy.
-What story?
-Nothing to tell you.
When it comes to sex,
you tell me nothing?
Sex?
No, no, no, no.
Nothing like that.
What is that?
GLOBAL AGENCY FOR GOVERNMENT OPERATIONS
My name
is Special Agent Alexandria Cortez.
If you're thinking
that this will be one of those
romantic love stories,
then you're mistaken.
So, let's start by getting to know
who the demon is that we are facing.
This is Viktor Valtrovi.
But don't be fooled.
Because the truth is,
Viktor Valtrovi is the head
of the Moraviano Syndicate.
But some people say
it was originally part of Cosa Nostra.
Do you like goulash?
My goulash is very good.
I'll give you goulash for free!
This is Congressman Celestino Salazar.
He was one of the first to investigate
the entry of foreign syndicates
into the country.
And clearly, it's a warning
by Viktor and the Moravianos
to anyone who wants to interfere
with their operations.
GLOBAL AGENCY FOR GOVERNMENT OPERATIONS
He's Michael D. Pinagpala.
Also known as Mikoy.
Chiara frequented the restaurant
where Mikoy works.
That's where they first met.
At first, we believed
their meeting was just accidental
and that they didn't really have
a deeper connection.
If I'm being honest,
I can't really blame Chiara
if she falls for Mikoy.
He's a good man.
He exudes an Enrique Gil vibe.
If Enrique Gil is a bit worn out by life.
Though if I am really being honest,
Piolo Pascual is more likely my type.
But it doesn't matter
if he's Enrique Gil or Papa P.
What matters
is that we now have a way to infiltrate
one of the most dangerous
syndicates in the world.
So Mikoy will be the key to our mission
in bringing down
this massive criminal syndicate.
It's cold.
Here's some coffee.
Is this really the only CCTV
that you can hack?
So he doesn't even have
CCTV inside his houses.
If there's no CCTV,
then we have nothing to hack.
Why, what happened?
Viktor is making a move.
He already had Mikoy kidnapped.
Huh?
What the heck! Why?
He probably discovered that
his daughter Chiara and Mikoy
are starting to like each other.
And now he has taken Mikoy
inside the house.
Actually, why am I even asking questions
when I already know the answer?
Yes.
It is very likely that he will intimidate
Mikoy to stay away from his daughter.
Maybe this will be the last time
we ever see this Mikoy.
I have no bad intentions toward her.
-Yes.
-No! No! No!
-Do not fool me, boy!
-Please! Please! Please!
I'm sorry.
Sorry, sir.
Viktor!
In Tagalog… What are you doing, huh?!
What are you doing? About to release him?
Release him?!
Don't lie to me! I know what you're doing!
You're trying to scare him
for our daughter!
She will be angry!
She will not talk to you for a year!
Would you like that?
Of course not!
Bad guy!
-Bad boy! Bad boy!
-Ouch!
By the way, I'm Donabel.
I am Chiara's mother.
The undisputed beauty queen
of Mabalacat, Pampanga!
Your turn.
Introduce yourself.
But with a Filipino heart
because of my wife.
And the global handsome guy,
Czech Charmer of Europe!
I'm sorry.
Sorry about my husband.
That's really how he is.
He does foolish things!
But he's a nice person, sometimes.
Right.
I am nice,
but only slightly.
Anyway, you were reported to us
by one of Chiara's bodyguards.
And I was very happy.
My daughter finally has a date!
Also, a fellow countryman, of course!
Where are you from?
Mikoy.
Mikoy? Well, I'm a beauty queen.
Charmer.
-You…
-I'm Mikoy Pinagpala.
Bisdak…
There…
Heartthrob?
Of…
-Cebu?!
-Yes!
-City!
-That's it!
Very good! Because of that,
you have to stay here for dinner.
So we can get to know each other, right?
-It's fine.
-Sweetheart?
Perfect!
We have adobo for dinner!
Okay, okay.
She is Donabel Dimaunahan.
From Mabalacat, Pampanga.
She met Viktor
when Donabel worked
as the caregiver of Viktor's mother.
And they were blessed with one child.
And her name is Chiara.
-I'm so happy!
-What is this?
Oh, perfect, dear! Here…
We invited him for dinner.
So we can all get to know each other.
Why is Mikoy here?
And who told you that he is my boyfriend?
How did you even know that I know him?
How many times do I have to say
that I don't want you
interfering in my life?
Dad, stop!
Okay? Stop.
Let's go.
Now you see what I have to go through
when it comes to my parents.
That's how they are.
They always keep
watching me wherever I go.
Whatever I do in my life, they interfere.
That's what I've been telling you.
Alex! Alex!
Alex, Mikoy is out.
He's with Chiara.
Are you even listening?
That's what I've been telling you.
That's why I feel suffocated
by the life they want for me.
Why didn't you tell me?
-That you're from a rich family.
-Huh?
Why?
How is that relevant, huh?
Does something have to change
just because my status in life is higher?
I'm just a waiter, Chiara.
And you?
This?
Our worlds are completely different.
And do you think I care?
You just don't understand.
Then make me understand.
And I think you like me, too.
So what's the problem?
I just want to go home.
This day has been too long already.
Okay fine, I'll have someone drive you.
No need.
Well, at least let me call you a cab.
Chiara.
I can manage on my own.
But thank you.
Okay, fine. If that's what you want.
You need strategy!
-Be careful with that.
-This way first.
-It's brand new.
-Here. Let's put it down here.
Oh, it's Mikoy!
Son, why did you call?
Wait a minute.
It's already night there, right?
Why aren't you resting yet?
I told you to be careful with it, Mario!
-That's very expensive, right?
-It's nothing!
It's just his knee.
The knee just gave out.
-That's what I'm saying.
-Just the knee.
Hey, son.
Do you remember
you gave us some extra money?
So, your Dad and I decided
to buy a new couch.
Well, our couch is already torn apart.
It's really old, son.
Wait, I'll show you.
Everybody!
Say hello to Mikoy!
Live via satellite
from the City of Prague!
Mikoy!
How are you, son?
Hello, Mikoy! Come home!
We miss you already!
Send us some booze!
Or some Czech girls!
Hey!
-That's it!
-Wait a sec!
Czech girls?
Well, son, why did you call?
Nothing, Mom.
Just checking in.
Nothing has changed here
in the Philippines.
You know, it's still chaotic.
You know, son,
a Congressman was killed here.
He's Partylist Congressman Salazar.
He was killed, son.
Wait a minute.
Why am I giving you bad news?
How are you doing there?
I'm okay, Mom.
Nothing's wrong.
Are you really okay?
I'm fine, Mom.
Mikoy, turn on your screen.
I want to see you.
What's the problem?
Who's messing with you?
Who's fighting with you?
Do you need backup?
Tell me, I'll deal with them!
Who is it?!
No one, Mom.
I'm really okay.
Mikoy!
Don't lie to your mom.
Because first of all,
there's high resolution
and high pixel density
in my phone's screen.
So, I can see in your eyes
if you have a problem.
Well, Mom,
I just got into a complicated situation.
You just admitted it!
Son.
How hard is your complicated situation?
It's about a girl, Mom.
We're in big trouble!
There's nothing we can do.
If you got her pregnant,
you have to take responsibility!
Oh, no!
Pregnant?
Who got pregnant?
Well, your son called.
He said he has a complicated situation.
He got involved with a woman.
We're going to be grandparents.
Mikoy!
That's not a complicated situation.
Actually, if you think about it,
children are truly a blessing.
The important thing
is you take responsibility.
You know in the Pinagpala family,
no one runs away
from their responsibilities.
And don't worry,
we'll help you raise the kids.
Mom! Dad! Wait a minute!
You're going the wrong way.
No one got pregnant!
I didn't get anyone pregnant,
nothing like that.
Then what is this
complicated situation you got into?
It's just that I met a girl.
And then?
Well, we kind of got serious.
There! Kaboom!
But she comes from a rich family, Dad.
And she's not just rich.
She's the daughter of one
of the richest families here in Prague.
That level!
Son, that's what you call a jackpot.
That's not a problem!
Stop it. Wait a minute.
Why?
Is her family snobbish?
Okay, hold on.
Tell me.
How's her attitude?
"You buy me this." "You buy me that."
Not really, Dad.
Actually, she's just simple.
She's fun to be with.
She's easygoing.
And she drinks a lot!
-So, what's the problem?
-Right.
Well, Mom,
even if you turn the world upside down,
we're not meant for each other.
She's like heaven!
And me,
I'm probably lower than the ground.
Like dirt.
You're putting yourself down too much.
Not really, Dad. But…
But what?
But I'm just being honest.
Because the poor don't usually end up
with the wealthy elite.
Son, I disagree with you.
You know this still happens.
The rich falls in love with the poor.
-It can happen.
-Yes.
Do you know any poor people
who ended up with the rich?
Tenten and Serena!
Huh?
Exactly, Mom.
It only happens on TV dramas.
Mikoy,
listen to me, okay?
Your worth is not measured by money.
Your worth is measured
by the depth of your heart.
The most important thing
is what you value the most.
Exactly!
Okay, Mom and Dad.
I love you.
I'll rest now.
This is Vicek, Hrobnik, and Pes.
CZECH CABLE COMPANY
The fact that Chiara
is still reaching out to Mikoy,
it means we still have a chance
to infiltrate the Moraviano Syndicate.
I really don't know
what she sees in Mikoy.
Look, he's just fair-skinned.
He has no sex appeal.
Looks like the Valtrovi's
only daughter got hit hard.
Stay here. I'll follow them.
Okay.
Wait!
Hey, buddy! Keep your channel open.
I hope you understand my fears.
I have fears, too.
If it's okay with you,
I'm ready to make it work.
Mr. Mikoy D. Pinagpala.
Is it okay that I already
introduced you to Mom and Dad?
It's not a problem.
I don't understand them.
My mom and dad don't trust people easily.
They have many enemies.
We are not the bad guys here, Mikoy.
Why should I believe you?
You might actually be the syndicate.
You already know what to do.